<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Real Estate Video Blog with Jeff Quintin</title>
    <description>Our mission at The Quintin Group is to be your best resource for real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The The Quintin Group, your professional Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 09:45:26 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 09:45:26 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Business Spotlight: Bungalow Bowls</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iUoHbwvsvL8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s business spotlight is on Bungalow Bowls. If you&amp;rsquo;ve never had an acai bowl before, you&amp;rsquo;re in for a treat.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m headed back into town today for another great business spotlight. &lt;strong&gt;Today we’re taking a closer look at Bungalow Bowls, the newest, hottest lunch spot here in Ocean City&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I joined co-owners Erin and Brooke, who fell in love with acai bowls on the west coast and decided to bring that here to Ocean City, for a demonstration of how they make their “Electric Feel” bowl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Electric Feel base starts with one fresh banana, two cups of frozen pineapple, and pitaya, which they put in a blender. Next, they add the “blue magic,” a spirulina extract which is great for your skin and gives you natural energy without any harsh taste. Then, they stir it up and top the base with granola, three different fresh fruits, and a honey drizzle on top. I picked blueberries, strawberries, and fresh pineapple for my bowl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The Electric Feel bowl was delicious.%20http://localhost:4000/business-spotlight-bungalow-bowls.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The Electric Feel bowl was delicious.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I was so excited to get to try my bowl, and I’ll certainly be back for another one soon&lt;/strong&gt;. If you want to know more about Bungalow Bowls, including their menu, their hours, and the superfoods they use to craft these delicious creations, you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bungalowbowls.com/&quot;&gt;visit their website here&lt;/a&gt;. Mention this video at the time of ordering and receive 10% off until September 7th.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information about Bungalow Bowls, including their menu and hours, visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bungalowbowls.com&quot;&gt;https://www.bungalowbowls.com/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions for me in the meantime, I’m always just a phone call or email away. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/business-spotlight-bungalow-bowls.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/business-spotlight-bungalow-bowls.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Business Spotlight</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
